Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum D
Yale University Divinity School Library
United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum D
1882-1996
RG 11D
Yale University Divinity School Library
7.5
(25 boxes)
This record group represents a continuation of the official archives of the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia, supplementing and overlapping the papers in record groups 11, 11A, 11B, and 11C. It provides information about the institutions and projects to which the United Board has lent its support. The United Board for Chrisian Higher Education in Asia supports educational work in China, Hong Kong, India, Indonesia, Japan, Korea, Pakistan, The Philippines, Republic of China (Taiwan).
United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Deposited by the UBCHEA.
Biographical / Historical
Information about the work of the United Board for Christian Higher Education during the period represented by these archives is contained in Paul Lauby's book Sailing on Winds of Change: Two Decades in the Life of the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia, 1969-1990.
Scope and Contents
The files have been maintained as sent by the United Board.
Arrangement
I. Organization and Policy Records. 1988 -1990
II. Committee Records, 1979-1992
III. Consolidated General File, 1979-1993
IV. Country Files, 1978-1992
V. Denominations/ Related Organizations, 1980-1990
VI. Conferences and Programs, 1981-1992
VII. Financial Records, 1979-1990
Religious education -- Asia; Universities and colleges -- Asia; Educators; Chong Ji shu yuan (Hong Kong, China); Dong hai da xue; Silliman University; United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia; Yŏnse Taehakkyo
- Organization and Policy Records, 1988 -1990; Series I
  - Board of Trustees meetings, 1988 Nov-1989 May (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees meetings, 1989 Sep-1990 May (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Presidental search, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Annual reports, 1967-1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Committee Records, 1979-1992; Series II
  - Agenda Committee
    - Correspondence, 1982 Aug-1987 Feb (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Development Committee
    - Minutes, agendas, correspondence, 1985 Nov-1986 Jul (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Minutes, agendas, correspondence, 1986 Sep-1987 Jun (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Minutes, agendas, correspondence, 1987 Oct-1988 Jun (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, agendas, correspondence, 1988 Jul- 1989 May (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Director of Development search, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Executive Committee
    - Records, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Records, 1985-1990 (Box 2, Folder 12-16)
  - Finance and Administration Committee
    - Records, 1985-1989 Jun (Box 2, Folder 17-20)
  - Investment and Banking Committee
    - Records, 1985-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21-25)
  - University Outreach Committee
    - Records, 1980-1988 (Box 2, Folder 26-29)
  - China Sub-Committee on Library and Translation Programs
    - Records, 1981 Jul-1882 Jun (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - China Concerns Sub-Committee
    - General, 1983 Jul-1984 Jun (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - General, 1984 Jul-1985 Jun (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Ad-Hoc China Concerns Sub-Committee, 1985 Jul- 1986 Jun (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - General, 1985 Jul-1986 Jun (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Sub-Committee on PRC Education, Sub-Committee on Amity Conference, 1986 Jul-1987 Jun (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - General, 1987 Jul-1988 Jun (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Nominations Committee
    - Records, 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 38-39)
  - Committee on Social Responsibility for Investments
    - Records, 1979-1988 (Box 3, Folder 40-41)
  - Women's Concerns Committee
    - Records, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Task Force on Women's Educational Concerns
    - Records, 1986-1988 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Personnel Resources Sub-Committee
    - China Program, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - China Program, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - China Program, 1979/80 and 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - China Program, 1990-1995 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Huan Ying Orientation Program, 1981 Jul- 1986 Jun (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - General, 1982-1989 (Box 5, Folder 51-55)
    - Personnel Subcommittee, 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - General, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Programs Policy Committee
    - General, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - General, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Process of Evaluation and Policy Development; Ad Hoc Committee for China Concerns, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - University Programs Subcommittee, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - University Programs Subcommitee, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - University Programs Subcommittee, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - China Library/Other Programs, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - China Coordinating Subcommittee, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - China Library/Other Programs, 1982-1985 (Box 6, Folder 66-68)
    - China Library/Other Programs, 1985-1988 (Box 7, Folder 69-71)
  - United Board China Delegation
    - General, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - United Board Asian Religion and Art Program
    - General, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Development Task Force
    - General, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Directions for the 90's Committee
    - General, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Investment Policies, Special Committees
    - Correspondence, Meetings, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Korean Advisory Committee
    - General, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - The Review/Planning/Rethinking Process Committee
    - General, 1980-1986 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - United Board Washington D.C. Support Committee
    - General, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - United Board Special Review and Planning Committee
    - General, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Silliman Committee - Special Commitee on Relations
    - General, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Ad Hoc Personnel Committee
    - General, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - United Board Asian Trustee Committee
    - General, 1983-1989 (Box 7, Folder 85)
- Consolidated General File, 1979-1993; Series III
  - Asher, Eva M., UB Donor, 1980-1988 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Asia North American Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Asia/North American Taxes, 1987-1989 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Asia/ North America Faculty Exchange Program, 1988-1990 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Asia Resource Center: Dr. Don Luce, 1980-1988 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - AWI Triennial Conference: Salatisa, Indonesia, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Association of Christian Universities and Colleges in Asia (ACUCA) - Proposals and grants, 1986-1993 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Beechy, Dr/Mrs. Atlee; UB Donors, 1980-1988 (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Bernstein, Sanford C. and Co., Investment Manager, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1983-1990 (Box 8, Folder 94a)
  - Mrs.Caluag, Josie - National Consultation on the Filipino Family, 1980-1988 (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Cammack Associates; President Mr. Charles W. Cammack III, 1984-1989 (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Chopra, Mr. and Mrs. Kewal and Jankek, UB Donors, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Chung, Phil-Kwong: Korea Visiting Professor, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Community Church, Deep River, Ontario, 1983-1989 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Conant, Miss Margaret, UB Donor, 1980-1988 (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Crain, Mrs. Sharon, 1984-1987 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Damanik, Prof. Konta Intan, Distinguished Visiting Asian Professor, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Del Carmen, Naricisso, Scholar, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Ensiner, Mr. Stuart M., United Board Counselor, 1980-1988 (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - Evangelische Zentralstelle fur Entwicklungshilfe, 1985-1987 (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - Fay, Dr. Ruth, 1980-1988 (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Frost, Dr. Loraine H., United Board Donor, 1980-1988 (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Garnett, Dr. W. Leslie, 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Gregorian, Mrs. Phebe, United Board Donor, 1980-1990 (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Grose, Dr. Robert, 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute, Grants and Proposals, 1987-1989 (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - Hoobler, Dr./Mrs. Sibley and Family, UB Donors, 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - Hsiao, Andrew, 1980-1985 (Box 8, Folder 113)
  - Hsu, Dr. F. Richard; President of China Institute in America, 1980-1989 (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - Investment Manager Search, United Board, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - Irving Trust, Bank of NY Takeover, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - Khaing, Prof. Daw, Mi Mi; Visiting Professor from Rangoon, Burma, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - Kim, Dr/Mrs. Byong-Suh (wife - Hyun-Soon), 1980-1990 (Box 9, Folder 118)
  - Kim, Dr. Yung-Chung, 1985-1990 (Box 9, Folder 119)
  - Koontz, Theodore and Gayle, 1988-1990 (Box 9, Folder 120)
  - Lauby, Paul - Honorary Dinner, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 121)
  - Lee, Rev. Miss Chung Chee, Associate General Secretary of The Hong Kong Council, 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 122)
  - Liu, Dr. Stephen C.Y., 1980-1989 (Box 9, Folder 123)
  - McAulay, Dr. Mrs. John D, 1980-1989 (Box 9, Folder 124)
  - McCord, Dr. James I, Chaiman of the United Board, 1987-1990 (Box 9, Folder 125)
  - McGregor, Rev/Mrs. Robert F., UB Donors, 1980-1988 (Box 9, Folder 126)
  - Mei, Dr./Mrs Y.P. (Yi-Pao Mai), 1980-1988 (Box 9, Folder 127)
  - Miller, Dr. Ed, 1980-1989 (Box 9, Folder 128)
  - Mount Holyoke College, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 129)
  - Ong, Dr. M. Shao-er, UB Donor, 1980-1988 (Box 9, Folder 130)
  - Park, Dr. Tae Kyu, Asian Visiting Professor, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 131)
  - Penney Memorial Church, 1980-1989 (Box 10, Folder 132)
  - Raymundo, Ramon and Laurie, 1986-1990 (Box 10, Folder 133)
  - Perry, Mr./Mrs. John C., 1984 (Box 10, Folder 134)
  - Selly Oak Colleges, England, 1981-1989 (Box 10, Folder 135)
  - Severinghaus, Dr. Sheldon R., 1980-1987 (Box 10, Folder 136)
  - Smith, Jr., Mrs. Datus C., UB Donor, 1981-1988 (Box 10, Folder 137)
  - Staff of UBCHEA - memos, staff positions, goals, outings, etc., 1978-1988 (Box 10, Folder 138)
  - Studley, Miss Ellen M., 1980-1988 (Box 10, Folder 139)
  - Tan, Miss Margaret Hee-Leng, 1983-1987 (Box 10, Folder 140)
  - Third World Scholars Consortium, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 141)
  - Thompson, Dr./Mrs. Kenneth H., 1980 (Box 10, Folder 142)
  - Tompkins, Dr. Pauline, 1980-1989 (Box 10, Folder 143)
  - Travel Agencies and Misc. Travel Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 144)
  - Tucker, Dr. W. Henry, 1981-1988 (Box 10, Folder 145)
  - Turk, Marsh, Kelly, and Hoare, UB's Counsel, 1984-1990 (Box 10, Folder 146)
  - Tyco, Dr. Perla R., Asian-North American Visiting Scholar, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 147)
  - Wall Hanging, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 148)
  - Wharton, Delores, Board of Trustees, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 149)
  - Whittemore, Rev. Edward L., 1980-1988 (Box 10, Folder 150)
  - Williams, Jr. Dr/ Mrs. M.D., 1980-1990 (Box 10, Folder 151)
  - Wolpert, Mrs. Gretchen C., 1981-1986 (Box 10, Folder 152)
  - Woo, Mrs. Jean, Asian Women's Institute, 1980-1989 (Box 10, Folder 153)
  - Wood, Struthers and Winthrop Management Corporation, 1981-1989 (Box 11, Folder 154)
  - Wu, Miss Blanche, 1982-1990 (Box 11, Folder 155)
- Country Files, 1978-1992; Series IV
  - China
    - Chiang Ching Dance Company, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 156)
    - China Claims Settlement, 1978-1982 (Box 11, Folder 157)
    - Tianamen Square Political Situation, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 158)
    - Foundation for East-West Trade Development, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 159)
    - Fujian Teachers University, 1988-1991 (Box 11, Folder 160)
    - Hangzhou Delegation to U.S., 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 161)
    - Hwa Nan Professional College for Women, 1985-1988 (Box 11, Folder 162)
    - Hwa Nan Professional School for Women, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 163)
    - Huang....A to Z (Box 11, Folder 164)
    - Institute of International Education, 1987-1989 (Box 11, Folder 165)
    - International Association of Historians of Asia, 1988-1991 (Box 11, Folder 166)
    - International Christian University, Zhang, Yong-Chang Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 167)
    - International Christian University, Shaanxi Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 12, Folder 168)
    - Lanzhou University General Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 12, Folder 169)
    - Liu, Dr. Chun Jo, 1989-1996 (Box 12, Folder 170)
    - Dr. Richard Madsen, Institute of American Studies, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 171)
    - Michigan State University, Sichuan, 1988-1992 (Box 12, Folder 172)
    - Nanjing Normal Universtiy, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 173)
    - China Princeton: Workshop on Comparative Cultures, 1988-1990 (Box 12, Folder 174)
    - Shaanxi Teachers University, 1988-1991 (Box 12, Folder 175)
    - Shanghai College of Education, Mr. Song Baoquan, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 176)
    - General SI-SNZ (Box 13, Folder 177)
    - Sichuan University, General, 1987-1990 (Box 13, Folder 178)
    - Suzhou University, 1985-1990 (Box 13, Folder 179)
    - General TI - TOZ (Box 13, Folder 180)
    - Tianjin Foreign Studies University/Institute, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 181)
    - Tibet National Committee on US-China Relations, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 182)
    - Xiamen University, 1986-1991 (Box 13, Folder 183)
    - Xinjing University, 1987-1991 (Box 13, Folder 184)
    - Yale-China Association, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 185)
    - Yu, Prof. Timothy, Communication Development Consultant, 1988-1991 (Box 14, Folder 186)
    - General YO-YZ (Box 14, Folder 187)
  - Hong Kong
    - University of Hong Kong Sino-American Relations Conference, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 188)
    - Hong Kong Baptist College - Proposals, grants, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 189)
    - Hong Kong Baptist College - Proposals, grants, 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 190)
    - Hong Kong Baptist College - Proposals, grants, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 191)
    - Chinese University of Hong Kong: Yee, Albert H. (Box 15, Folder 192)
    - Chinese University of Hong Kong: Project reports, 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 193)
    - Chinese University of Hong Kong, 1987-1990 (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Chung Chi College - Proposals, grants, etc, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 195)
    - Chung Chi College - Proposals, grants, etc, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 196)
    - Chung Chi College - Propoals, grants, etc, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 197)
    - Chung Chi College - Proposals, grants, etc, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 198)
  - India
    - Manickman, Sundararaj; Visiting Professor, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - Masilamani, Dr. Nithila and Dr. John D.; Visiting Professors from the Women's Christian College, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 201)
    - Peeradina, Salem; Visiting Professor, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 202)
    - Timbreza, Prof. Florenino; Asian Visiting Professor De La Salle College, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 203)
    - Sahayam, Dr. and Mrs. S. John, The American College India Asian Visiting Professor, 1987-1995 (Box 16, Folder 204)
    - Pasaribu, Dr. Amudi; Asia North American Faculty Exchange Program, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 205)
    - Belita, Rev. Father Jimmy A from De La Salle Unjversity Visiting Professor, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 206)
    - A.I.A.C.H.E. proposals, grants, etc, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 207)
    - A.I.A.C.H.E. proposals, grants, etc, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 208)
    - A.I.A.C.H.E. proposals, grants, etc, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 209)
    - India Program projects, 1988-1991 (Box 16, Folder 210)
    - The American College, Madurai, 1983-1992 (Box 16, Folder 211)
  - Indonesia
    - Universitas HKBP Nommensen University, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 212)
    - Universitas HKBP Nommensen, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 213)
    - Universitas HKBP Nommensen; Professor Dr. Amudi Pasaribu, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 214)
    - Petra University; correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 215)
    - Petra University; proposals, grants, etc, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 216)
    - Petra University; proposals, grants, etc, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 217)
    - Petra Universtiy; proposals, grants, etc, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 218)
    - Satya Wacana Christian University; photographs, slides, etc, 1980-1990 (Box 16, Folder 219)
    - Satya Wacana Christian University; grants, proposals, etc, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 220)
    - Satya Wacana Christian University; grants, proposals, etc, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 221)
  - Japan
    - International Christian Universtiy; grants, proposals, etc, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 222)
    - International Christian University; grants, proposals, etc, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 223)
    - International Christian University; grants, proposals, etc, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 224)
    - Sophia University - Overseas Personnel Lists, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 225)
    - Hashiguchi, Prof. Tomosuke; President of Sophia University, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 226)
    - Sophia University Background; Profiles, questionnaires, etc, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 227)
    - Sophia University: Yanase, Rev. Michael M, President, 1981-1984 (Box 17, Folder 228)
    - Sophia University; grants and proposals, 1979-1984 (Box 17, Folder 229)
    - Sophia University; proposals, grants, 1984-1990 (Box 17, Folder 230)
    - Tokyo Women's Christian University, 1980-1990 (Box 17, Folder 231)
  - Korea
    - Christian Faculty Fellowship, 1980-1989 (Box 17, Folder 232)
    - Ewha Women's University; proposals and grants, 1986-1988 (Box 17, Folder 233)
    - Ewha Women's University; proposals and grants, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 234)
    - Ewha Women's University; Chung, Dr. Il Sook/Hoo-Jung (President), 1980-1989 (Box 17, Folder 235)
    - Ham Nam University; proposals and grants, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 236)
    - Ham Nam University; proposals and grants, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 237)
    - Sogang University; proposals and grants, 1987-1989 (Box 18, Folder 238)
    - Sogang University; proposals and grants, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 239)
    - Sogang University; Paul Sye (President) correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box 18, Folder 240)
    - Soong Sil University; proposals and grants, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 241)
    - Soong Sil University; proposals and grants, 1985-1988 (Box 18, Folder 242)
    - Soong Sil University; proposals and grants, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 243)
    - Soong Sil University; Dr. Johann Zoh correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 244)
    - Soong Sil University; Chi Sun Kim (President) correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 18, Folder 245)
    - Yonsei University; proposals and grants, 1986-1989 (Box 18, Folder 246)
    - Yonsei University; proposals and grants, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 247)
    - Yonsei University; Project report, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 248)
    - Yonsei University Medical Center, 1980-1990 (Box 18, Folder 249)
    - Yonsei University Medical Center Severence Alumni Association (Box 18, Folder 250)
    - Yonsei University Medical Center Orthopedic Travelling Fellowship, 1980-1990 (Box 18, Folder 251)
  - Philippines
    - Central Philippines University Library Project, 1987-1991 (Box 19, Folder 252)
    - Central Philippines University Institutional Profile, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 253)
    - Central Philippines Universtiy; proposals and grants, 1988-1990 (Box 19, Folder 254)
    - Brokenshire College; Dr. Marcllo Satentes (President), 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 255)
    - AILM correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 256)
    - De La Salle University; proposals and grants, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 257)
    - B General (Box 19, Folder 258)
    - C General (Box 19, Folder 259)
    - I General (Box 19, Folder 260)
    - N General (Box 19, Folder 261)
    - O,S,V,W General (Box 20, Folder 262)
    - Inter-institutional Consortium Philippines; proposals and grants, 1986-1988 (Box 20, Folder 263)
    - Inter-institutional Consortium Philippines; proposals and grants, 1988-1990 (Box 20, Folder 264)
    - Northern Christian College; Dr. Reuben R. Batoon (Preisdent), 1987-1990 (Box 20, Folder 265)
    - Northern Christian College Institutional Profile, 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 266)
    - Northern Christian College; proposals and grants, 1988-1990 (Box 20, Folder 267)
    - Loan from UB Revolving Loan Fund to Philippine Christian University, 1980-1990 (Box 20, Folder 268)
    - Philippine Christian University; proposals and gratns, 1987-1989 (Box 20, Folder 269)
    - St. Scholastica's College, 1987-1989 (Box 20, Folder 270)
    - Silliman University; Pedro V. FLores (President), 1987-1989 (Box 20, Folder 271)
    - Silliman Universtiy; proposals and grants, 1988-1990 (Box 20, Folder 272)
    - Silliman University; Presco Udarbe correpondence, 1987-1989 (Box 20, Folder 273)
    - Silliman University; Dr. Lourdino Yuzon (President), 1987-1990 (Box 21, Folder 274)
    - Southern Christian College; proposals and grants, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 275)
    - Southern Christian College; proposals and grants, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 276)
    - Southern Christian College Institutional Profile, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 277)
    - Trinity College; proposals and grants, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 278)
    - Trinity College; proposals and grants, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 279)
    - Trinity College; proposals and grants, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 280)
    - Trinity College Institutional Profile, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 281)
  - Taiwan
    - Soochow University; profiles, 1988-1990 (Box 21, Folder 282)
    - Soochow University; Mr. and Mrs. John Exter (Donors), 1980-1991 (Box 21, Folder 283)
    - Tunghai University; proposals, grants, loans, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 284)
    - Tunghai University; proposals, grants, loans, 1988-1990 (Box 21, Folder 285)
- Denominations/ Related Organizations, 1980-1990; Series V
  - American Baptist Churches USA; proposals and grants, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 287)
  - American Baptist Churches USA; proposals and grants, 1987-1990 (Box 21, Folder 288)
  - Christian Church (Disciples of Christ); proposals and grants, 1986-1990 (Box 21, Folder 289)
  - Union Christian College, 1987-1989 (Box 21, Folder 290)
  - Episcopal Church (Executive Council in NYC); proposals and grants, 1987-1989 (Box 21, Folder 291)
  - Evangelical Lutheran Church in America; proposals and grants, 1987-1990 (Box 21, Folder 292)
  - Executive Committee correspondence: Division of Overseas Ministries, 1980-1990 (Box 21, Folder 293)
  - Finance; Askings and UB grants, 1982-1989 (Box 21, Folder 294)
  - Unit Committee Material: Division of Overseas Ministries, 1980-1988 (Box 21, Folder 295)
  - Presbyterian Church in Canada correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 22, Folder 296)
  - Presbyterian Church in Canada; Board of World Mission; proposals and grants, 1986-1988 (Box 22, Folder 297)
  - Presbyterian Church USA; proposals and grants, 1986-1989 (Box 22, Folder 298)
  - Presbyterian Church USA; Program Agency in NY; finance, grants, correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 22, Folder 299)
  - United Church of Canada; proposals and grants, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 300)
  - United Church of Canada; proposals and grants, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 301)
  - United Church Board for World Ministries, United Church of Christ - finance, grants, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 302)
  - United Church Board for World Ministries, United Church of Christ- finance, grants, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 303)
  - United Church Board for World Ministries, United Church of Christ- finance, grants, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 304)
  - United Methodist Church, 1987-1989 (Box 22, Folder 305)
  - United Methodist Church, Global Ministries/World Division, 1987-1990 (Box 22, Folder 306)
- Conferences and Programs, 1981-1992; Series VI
  - Nanjing Colloquium: Dr. Mary B. Bullock, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 307)
  - Nanjing Colloquium: Dr. Peter Seybolt, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 308)
  - Nanjing Colloquium: Dr. Kiyoko Cho, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 309)
  - Nanjing Colloquium: D. Lawrence Lau, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 310)
  - Nanjing Colloquium: Dr. Ruth Hayhoe, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 311)
  - Women for Asian Development; finances, correspondence, misc., 1988-1992 (Box 23, Folder 312)